Guide to the Jerome New Frank Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- UNITED STATES COURT OF APPEALS FOR THE SECOND CIRCUIT (CA II), 1941-1957; Series V; 22.5; (54 boxes)
  - Opinions
    - DeFilippis v. Chrysler Sales Corporation, No. 230 (1942 Apr 6) (Box 77, Folder 169)
    - Della Vecchia v. Fairchild Engine & Airplane Corporation, No. 99 (1948 Nov 29) (Box 77, Folder 170)
    - DeNobili Cigar Company v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 92 (1944 May 22) (Box 77, Folder 171)
    - Denton & Anderson Company v. Induction Heating Corporation, No. 87 (1949 Dec 5) (Box 77, Folder 172)
    - Desmond v. United States of America, No. 43 (1954 Oct 4) (Box 77, Folder 173)
    - Diamond and Bruen v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, Nos. 102-103 (1954 Dec 13), 1955 (Box 77, Folder 174)
    - Diamond, Estate of v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 106 (1947 Jan 13) (Box 77, Folder 175)
    - Diaz v. Lykes Bros. Steamship Co., Inc., No. 219 (1956 Jan 9) (Box 77, Folder 176)
    - Dimas v. Lehigh Valley Railroad Company, No. 298 (1956 Apr 2) (Box 77, Folder 177)
    - Dincher v. The Marlin Firearms Co., No. 263 (1952 May 12) (Box 77, Folder 178)
    - Dix (J. J.), Inc., et al. v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, Nos. 23-24 (1955 Apr 18) (Box 77, Folder 179)
    - Dixon v. American Telephone and Telegraph Company, No. 91 (1947 Jan 13) (Box 77, Folder 180)
    - Dodge (A. C.) Diesel Tanker, Inc., In re, No. 344 (1956 May 7) (Box 77, Folder 181)
    - Dodge (A. C.) Diesel Tanker, Inc. v. J. M. Carras, Inc., No. 124 (1955 Jan 10) (Box 77, Folder 182)
    - Doehler Metal Furniture Company, Inc. v. United States of America, No. 287 (1945 Apr 2) (Box 77, Folder 183)
    - Dominick, Estate of v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 56 (1945 Dec 10), 1946 (Box 77, Folder 184)
    - Dornhofer v. The Long Island Railroad Company, No. 96 (1943 Oct 18) (Box 77, Folder 185)
    - Douds v. Local 1250, Retail Wholesale Department Store Union of America, No. 86 [canceled] (1948 Oct 11) (Box 77, Folder 186)
    - Drinkhouse v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 262 (1955 May 9) (Box 77, Folder 187)
    - Drittel v. Friedman, No. 230 (1946 Mar 11) (Box 77, Folder 188)
    - Dugan v. Lear, Incorporated, No. 218 (1946 Mar 11) (Box 77, Folder 189)
    - Duke v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue No. 44 (1952 Oct 6) (Box 77, Folder 190)
    - Duquesne Warehouse Company v. Railroad Retirement Board, No. 138 (1945 Jan 8) (Box 77, Folder 191)
    - Dyer, et al. v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, Nos. 36-40 (1954 Feb 1) (Box 77, Folder 192)
    - Dyer v. MacDougall, No. 17 (1952 Oct 6) (Box 77, Folder 193)
    - Eastern Wine Corporation v. Winslow-Warren Ltd., Incorporated, No. 272 (1943 May 3) (Box 77, Folder 194)
    - Eddy v. Kelby, No. 153 (1947 Jan 13) (Box 77, Folder 195)
    - Eder v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, Nos. 244-246 (1943 Jun 14) (Box 77, Folder 196)
    - Elizabeth Arden, Inc. v. Federal Trade Commission, No. 60 (1946 May 13) (Box 77, Folder 197)
    - Emery v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 67 (1947 Dec 8), 1948 (Box 77, Folder 198)
    - Engel v. F. W. Woolworth v. Otis Elevator Company, No. 232 (1954 Apr 5) (Box 77, Folder 199)
    - Erie Railroad Company v. Tug "Cornell No. 20," et al., No. 80 (1947 Nov 10) (Box 77, Folder 200)
    - Falk v. Levy, No. 159 (1950 Feb 6) (Box 77, Folder 201)
    - Fanelli v. United States Gypsum Company, No. 245 (1944 Jan 31) (Box 77, Folder 202)
    - Farm Bureau Mutual Automobile Insurance Company v. Violano, No. 54 (1941 Nov 3) (Box 77, Folder 203)
    - Federal Glass Co. v. Loshin (1954 Oct 4) (Box 77, Folder 204)
    - Federal Trade Commission v. Standard Brands, Incorporated, No. 73 (1951 Feb 5) (Box 77, Folder 205)
    - Feist (Leo), Inc. and Twentieth Century Music Corporation v. Song Parodies, Inc., Nos, 186-187 (1944 Dec 11) (Box 77, Folder 206)
    - Feuerstein v. Zukor, No. 218 (1949 Apr 4) (Box 77, Folder 207)
    - Field, Estate of v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 202 (1944 Jun 12) (Box 77, Folder 208)
    - Field v. The Witt Tire Company of Atlanta, Georgia, Incorporated, No. 57 (1952 Oct 6) (Box 77, Folder 209)
    - Fifth Avenue-14th Street Corporation v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 42 (1944 Nov 13) (Box 77, Folder 210)
    - Fifty-Eighth Street Plaza Theatre, Inc. v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, Nos 142-143 (1952 Jan 7) (Box 77, Folder 211)
    - Fischman v. Raytheon Manufacturing Company, No. 190 (1951 Mar 12) (Box 77, Folder 212)
    - Fitzgerald, et al. v. Pan American World Airways, Inc., No. 234 (1956 Jan 9) (Box 78, Folder 213)
    - Flatbush Avenue-Nevins Street Corporation, In re, No. 150 (1942 Dec 14), 1943 (Box 78, Folder 214)
    - Fleetwood Acres, Inc. v. Federal Housing Administration, No. 84 (1948 Nov 29) (Box 78, Folder 215)
    - Fleming v. Post, No. 125 (1944 Nov 13) (Box 78, Folder 216)
    - Fodera v. Booth American Shipping Corp., No. 162 (1947 Jan 13) (Box 78, Folder 217)
    - Ford Motor Company v. Honorable Sylvester J. Ryan (1950 Mar 6) (Box 78, Folder 218)
    - Foster v. Moore-McCormack Lines, Inc., No. 66 (1942 Oct 19) (Box 78, Folder 219)
    - Franke v. Wiltschek, et al., No. 96 (1953 Oct 5) (Box 78, Folder 220)
    - Frankel & Smith Beauty Departments, Inc. v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 190 (1948 Mar 1) (Box 78, Folder 221)
    - Fratta v. Grace Lines, Inc., No. 58 (1943 Nov 1) (Box 78, Folder 222)
    - Fried, In re, No. 168 (1947 Feb 3) (Box 78, Folder 223)
    - Galdi v. Jones, No. 269 (1944 Mar 6) (Box 78, Folder 224)
    - Gannett Co., Inc. v. Larry, No. 209 (1955 Feb 14) (Box 78, Folder 225)
    - Gardella v. Chandler, No. 98 (1948 Nov 29), 1949 (Box 78, Folder 226)
    - Geist v. Prudence Realization Corporation, No. 343 (1941 Jun 9) (Box 78, Folder 227)
    - Gelson v. Rudin, No. 81 (1952 Oct 6) (Box 78, Folder 228)
    - General Aniline & Film Corporation v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 73 (1943 Dec 13), 1944 (Box 78, Folder 229)
    - General Artists Corporation v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 209 (1953 Apr 13) (Box 78, Folder 230)
    - General Plastics, Inc. v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 14 (1944 Oct 16) (Box 78, Folder 231)
    - General Stores Corporation v. Shlensky and Securities and Exchange Commission, No. 261 (1955 Mar 14) (Box 78, Folder 232)
    - General Time Instruments Corporation v. The United States Time Corporation, No. 114 (1947 Dec 8), 1948 (Box 78, Folder 233)
    - Gevirtz v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 17 (1941 Oct 20) (Box 78, Folder 234)
    - Gilbert v. Gulf Oil Corporation, No. 167 (1946 Jan 7) (Box 78, Folder 235)
    - Goldblatt v. Inch (1954 Mar 2), 1953 (Box 78, Folder 236)
    - Golden Eagle Farm Products, Inc. v. Approved Dehydrating Co., Inc., No. 208 (1945 Jan 8) (Box 78, Folder 237)
    - Goldman v. American Dealers Service, Inc., No. 215 (1943 Mar 8) (Box 78, Folder 238)
    - Golin v. Florence Trading Corporation, No. 264 (1942 May 4) (Box 78, Folder 239)
    - Goumas v. K. Karras & Son and S. S. Karras, No. 221 (1944 Jan 10) (Box 78, Folder 240)
    - Gowanda Cooperative Saving and Loan Association v. Gray, No. 246 (1950 Jun 5) (Box 78, Folder 241)
    - Grace (W. R.) & Co. v. Civil Aeronautics Board, No. 92 (1945 Nov 12), 1946 (Box 78, Folder 242)
    - Grant v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 42 (1953 Nov 9) (Box 78, Folder 243)
    - Grant v. Kellogg Company, No. 207 (1946 Feb 11) (Box 78, Folder 244)
    - Granz v. Harris, No. 240 (1952 May 12) (Box 78, Folder 245)
    - Great Lakes Dredge & Dock Company v. The S. S. Santiago, No. 255 (1946 Apr 1) (Box 78, Folder 246)
    - Great Lakes Transit Corporation and Levisohn v. Marceau, No. 191 (1946 Feb 4) (Box 78, Folder 247)
    - Green, Ex parte, No. 104 (1941 Oct 20) (Box 78, Folder 248)
    - Guiseppi v. Walling, No. 361 (1944 May 22) (Box 78, Folder 249)
    - Gunlock (W. H.) Chair Company v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 62 (1944 Oct 16) (Box 78, Folder 250)
    - Guttmann v. Illinois Central Railroad Company, No. 238 (1951 Apr 30) (Box 78, Folder 251)
    - Hackner v. Morgan, No. 325 (1942 Jun 15) (Box 78, Folder 252)
    - Haelan Laboratories, Inc. v. Topps Chewing Gum, Inc., No. 158(1953 Jan 5) (Box 78, Folder 253)
    - Hagens v. United Fruit Company, No. 253 (1943 May 3) (Box 78, Folder 254)
    - Halpert v. Engine Air Service, Inc., No. 154 (1953 Dec 14), 1954 (Box 78, Folder 255)
    - Hamilton Watch Company v. Benrus Watch Company, No. 283 (1953 Jun 1) (Box 78, Folder 256)
    - Hammond-Knowlton v. United States of America, No. 302 (1941 May 19) (Box 79, Folder 257)
    - Harris v. Twentieth Century-Fox Film Corporation, No. 72 (1943 Oct 11) (Box 79, Folder 258)
    - Hartford Electric Light Company v. Federal Power Commission, No. 42 (1942 Nov 2) (Box 79, Folder 259)
    - Heagney v. Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal, No. 249 (1951 Jun 4) (Box 79, Folder 260)
    - Heier and Larsen v. Panama Transport Company, No. 140 (1949 Jan 10) (Box 79, Folder 261)
    - Heim v. Universal Pictures Co., Inc. No. 178 (1946 Jan 7) (Box 79, Folder 262)
    - Hentschel, et al. v. Baby Bathinette Corporation, et al., No. 251 (1954 Apr 5) (Box 79, Folder 263)
    - Herzig v. Swift & Co., No. 153 (1944 Dec 11), 1945 (Box 79, Folder 264)
    - Hickerson v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 112 (1955 Dec 5), 1956 (Box 79, Folder 265)
    - Hickey v. Chahoon, No. 88 (1945 Dec 10), 1946 (Box 79, Folder 266)
    - Hirsch Improvement Company, The v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 55 (1944 May 1) (Box 79, Folder 267)
    - Hochschild v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 186 (1947 Mar 10) (Box 79, Folder 268)
    - Hoffman v. Palmer, et al., Tr., No. 261 (1942 May 4) (Box 79, Folder 269)
    - Hoyt v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 63 (1944 Oct 16) (Box 79, Folder 270)
    - Hume v. Moore-McCormack Lines, Inc., No. 294 (1941 May 12) (Box 79, Folder 271)
    - Hunter v. United States of America, No. 132 (1955 Jan 10) (Box 79, Folder 272)
    - Indemnity Insurance Company of North America v. Reisley, No. 137 (1945 Nov 12) (Box 79, Folder 273)
    - Indemnity Insurance Company of North America v. Silver, No. 50 (1949 Oct 10) (Box 79, Folder 274)
    - Independent Employees Association of the Neptune Meter Company v. National Labor Relations Board, Nos. 70, 78-79 (1946 Nov 4) (Box 79, Folder 275)
    - Ingo v. Koch, No. 122 (1941 Dec 8), 1942 (Box 79, Folder 276)
    - International Freighting Corporation, Inc. v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 5 (1943 Feb 1) (Box 79, Folder 277)
    - International Match Corporation, In re; Ehrhorn v. International Realization Co., Ltd., Nos. 185-186 (1951 Mar 5) (Box 79, Folder 278)
    - International Spotlight Corporation v. Casco Products Corporation, No. 166 (1949 Mar 7) (Box 79, Folder 279)
    - International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers, CIO, et al. v. Underwood Corporation, No. 182 (1954 Dec 13), 1955 (Box 79, Folder 280)
    - Irwin v. Simmons, No. 233 (1944 Jan 10) (Box 79, Folder 281)
    - Jackson v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 267 (1956 Apr 2) (Box 79, Folder 282)
    - Janeway v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, Nos. 29-30 (1945 Jan 8) (Box 79, Folder 283)
    - Johansen v. United States of America, No. 275 (1951 Apr 30) (Box 79, Folder 284)
    - Johnson (R. H.) & Company v. Securities and Exchange Commissions No. 267 (1952 Jun 2) (Box 79, Folder 285)
    - Johnson v. United States of America, No. 230 (1948 Apr 12) (Box 79, Folder 286)
    - Johnston Warren Lines Ltd. v. United States of America, No. 221 (1952 Apr 4) (Box 79, Folder 287)
    - Joint Council Dining Car Employees Local v. Delaware, Lackawanna and Western Railroad Company, No. 272 (1946 May 13) (Box 79, Folder 288)
    - Jones v. United States of America, No. 14 (1953 Oct 5) (Box 79, Folder 289)
    - Joseph v. Farnsworth Radio and Television Corp., No. 252 (1952 May 12) (Box 79, Folder 290)
    - Katz v. Horni Signal Manufacturing Corporation, No. 76 (1944 Oct 16) (Box 79, Folder 291)
    - Kaufman & Ruderman, Inc. v. Cohn & Rosenberger, Inc., No. 56 (1949 Oct 10) (Box 79, Folder 292)
    - Kelcey v. Tankers Company Incorporated, No. 77 (1954 Oct 4) (Box 79, Folder 293)
    - Keller v. Brooklyn Bus Corporation, No. 247 (1942 Apr 6) (Box 79, Folder 294)
    - Kelly Trust #2, et al. v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, Nos. 154-159 (1948 May 10) (Box 79, Folder 295)
    - Ketcham v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 295 (1944 May 1) (Box 80, Folder 296)
    - Kind v. Clark, No. 206 (1947 Mar 10) (Box 80, Folder 297)
    - Kirby v. The Pittsburgh Courier Publishing Co., Inc., No. 357 (1945 Jun 4) (Box 80, Folder 298)
    - Klein v. Securities and Exchange Commission, No. 298 (1955 May 9) (Box 80, Folder 299)
    - Kleinman v. Kobler, No. 155 (1956 Jan 9) (Box 80, Folder 300)
    - Knetzer v. Larkin, No. 84 (1949 Dec 5) (Box 80, Folder 301)
    - Koehler v. Presque-Isle Transportation Co., No. 279 (1944 Mar 6) (Box 80, Folder 302)
    - Kolb, In re, No. 94 (1945 Oct 8) (Box 80, Folder 303)
    - Komlos v. Compagnie Nationale Air France, No. 59 (1953 Nov 9) (Box 80, Folder 304)
    - Kreste v. United States of America, No. 64 (1946 Nov 4) (Box 80, Folder 305)
    - Kulukundis Shipping Co., S/A v. Amborg Trading Corporation, No. 170 (1942 Feb 2) (Box 80, Folder 306)
    - Kushelewitz v. The National City Bank of New York, No. 169 (1953 Feb 2) (Box 80, Folder 307)
    - Lago Oil and Transport Company, Ltd. v. United States of America, No. 232 (1956 Feb 13) (Box 80, Folder 308)
    - Lake Tankers Corporation, In re petition of, No. 268 (1956 Feb 13) (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Landon v. United States of America, No. 207 1952 (1952 Mar 10) (Box 80, Folder 310)
    - Lapides v. United States of America, 1954 No. 109 (1954 Mar 1) (Box 80, Folder 311)
    - Larsen v. New York Dock Company, No. 184 (1948 Mar 1) (Box 80, Folder 312)
    - Larsen v. Wright & Cobb Lighterage Company; Knudsen v. Lee & Simmons, Inc., Nos. 177-178 (1948 Mar 1) (Box 80, Folder 313)
    - Larson v. Jo Ann Cab Corporation, No. 88 (1953 Dec 14), 1954 (Box 80, Folder 314)
    - LaTouraine Coffee Co., Inc. v. Lorraine Coffee Company, Inc. and Eben, No. 300 (1946 May 13) (Box 80, Folder 315)
    - Lehman v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 228 (1942 Jun 8) (Box 80, Folder 316)
    - Lester v. United States of America, No. 269 (1956 Mar 12) (Box 80, Folder 317)
    - Leventritt v. Securities and Exchange Commission (1949 Oct 10) (Box 80, Folder 318)
    - Levesque v. F. H. McGraw & Co. and Purdy & Henderson Co., Inc.; Tetrault v. F. H. McGraw & Co. and Purdy & Henderson Co., Inc., Nos. 116-117 (1947 Dec 8), 1948 (Box 80, Folder 319)
    - Libby-Owens-Ford Glass Company v. Sylvania Industrial Corporation and Sylvania Plastics, Inc. (1946 Feb 11) (Box 80, Folder 320)
    - Lichten v. Eastern Airlines, Inc. No. 166 (1951 Feb 4) (Box 80, Folder 321)
    - Linahan, Inc., In re, No. 99 (1942 Dec 14), 1943 (Box 80, Folder 322)
    - Linahan, Inc., In re, Nos. 142-143 (1943 Oct 11) (Box 80, Folder 323)
    - Lindeman, et al. v. Textron Incorporated, No. 183 (1955 Dec 5), 1956 (Box 80, Folder 324)
    - Lobel v. American Airlines, Inc., No. 14 (1951 Oct 1) (Box 80, Folder 325)
    - Lo Bue v. United States of America and Jarka Corporation, No. 125 (1950 Dec 11), 1951 (Box 80, Folder 326)
    - Loewer's (V.) Gambrinus Brewery Co., Inc., In re, No. 188 (1948 Mar 1) (Box 80, Folder 327)
    - Loewi, et al. v. Ryan, et al., Nos. 100-101 (1955 Nov 14), 1956 (Box 80, Folder 328)
    - Loughman v. Town of Pelham, No. 43 1943 (1943 Oct 18) (Box 80, Folder 329)
    - Low v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 67 (1946 Feb 4) (Box 80, Folder 330)
    - Lowerree, In re, No. 43 (1946 Oct 7) (Box 80, Folder 331)
    - Lukens Steel Company v. American Locomotive Company, No. 219 (1952 Apr 14) (Box 80, Folder 332)
    - Luma Camera Service, Inc., In re, No. 31 (1946 Oct 7) (Box 80, Folder 333)
    - McAllister v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 266 (1946 Jun 10) (Box 80, Folder 334)
    - McClelland v. Greenberg, No. 225 (1944 Jan 10) (Box 80, Folder 335)
    - McComb v. Frank Scerbo & Sons, Inc., No. 235 (1949 Jun 6) (Box 80, Folder 336)
    - McComb v. Utica Knitting Company, No. 49 (1947 Oct 13) (Box 80, Folder 337)
    - McCullough v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 16 (1945 Nov 12), 1946 (Box 80, Folder 338)
    - Machaty v. Astra Pictures, Inc. and Astra Pictures, Inc. v. Eureka Productions, Inc., Nos. 180-181 (1952 Feb 11) (Box 81, Folder 339)
    - Madeirense Do Brasil S/A v. Stulman-Emrick Lumber Co., No. 108 (1944 Nov 6), 1945 (Box 81, Folder 340)
    - Magnetic Engineering & Manufacturing Co. v. Dings Manufacturing Co., No. 86 (1949 Dec 5), 1950 (Box 81, Folder 341)
    - Magnussen v. Ocean Steamship Company of Savannah, No. 227 (1947 May 5) (Box 81, Folder 342)
    - Mahaffey, In re, No. 256 (1942 Apr 6) (Box 81, Folder 343)
    - Mahar v. Gartland Steamship Company, No. 217 (1946 Mar 11) (Box 81, Folder 344)
    - Malman v. United States of America, No. 138 (1953 Jan 5) (Box 81, Folder 345)
    - Manger v. Kree Institute of Electrolysis, No. 303 (1956 Apr 2) (Box 81, Folder 346)
    - Marchessault v. National Grange Mutual Liability Company, No. 125 (1955 Dec 5), 1956 (Box 81, Folder 347)
    - Margiotta v. District Director of Internal Revenue, Brooklyn, New York, No. 280 (1954 Jun 7) (Box 81, Folder 348)
    - Marine Harbor Properties, Inc., No. 107 (1941 Oct 20), 1942 (Box 81, Folder 349)
    - Marks and Tanzer v. Higgins, No. 240 (1954 May 3) (Box 81, Folder 350)
    - Martin v. Campanero, No. 290 (1946 May 13) (Box 81, Folder 351)
    - Martin v. McAllister Lighterage Line, Inc., No. 219 (1953 Apr 13) (Box 81, Folder 352)
    - Martin v. Rose, No. 238 (1949 May 2) (Box 81, Folder 353)
    - Massachusetts Universalist Convention v. Hildreth & Rogers Company (CA I decisions), 1949 (Box 81, Folder 354)
    - Mastercrafters Clock & Radio Co. v. Vacheron & Constantin-Le Coultre Watches, Inc., No. 194 (1955 Feb 14) (Box 81, Folder 355)
    - Mastrapasqua v. Shaughnessy, No. 140 (1950 Jan 9) (Box 81, Folder 356)
    - Mayer Tank Manufacturing Company, Inc. v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 127 (1942 Feb 2) (Box 81, Folder 357)
    - Mechanical Ice Tray Corporation, et al. V. General Motors Corporation, No. 378 (1944 Jun 12) (Box 81, Folder 358)
    - Merrill v. United States of America, No. 101 (1945 Nov 12) (Box 81, Folder 359)
    - Metal Associates, Inc. v. East Side Metal Spinning & Stamping Corporation, No. 74 (1947 Nov 10) (Box 81, Folder 360)
    - Meyer and Mokava Corporation v. Dolan, No. 132 (1944 Dec 11), 1945 (Box 81, Folder 361)
    - Michaelson v. Herren, No. 131 (1956 Oct 1) (Box 81, Folder 362)
    - Michelsen v. Penney, No. 124 (1942 Dec 14), 1943 (Box 81, Folder 363)
    - Miller v. Browning Steamship Company, No. 115 (1947 Dec 8) (Box 81, Folder 364)
    - Miller v. The National City Bank of New York and Guaranty Trust Company of New York, No. 124 (1948 Feb 2) (Box 81, Folder 365)
    - Mirsky, In re, No. 128 (1941 Dec 8), 1942 (Box 81, Folder 366)
    - Mitchell v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 27 (1951 Feb 5) (Box 81, Folder 367)
    - Moffett v. Arabian American Oil Company, Inc., No. 33 (1950 Oct 9) (Box 81, Folder 368)
    - Moffett v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 220 (1951 Jun 4) (Box 81, Folder 369)
    - Mokava Corporation and Meyer v. Dolan, No. 132 (1944 Dec 11), 1945 (Box 81, Folder 370)
    - Mollenberg, Estate of v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 167 (1949 Mar 7) (Box 81, Folder 371)
    - Montoya v. Tide Water Associated Oil Company, No. 174 (1949 Feb 14) (Box 81, Folder 372)
    - Monza Mills, Inc., In re, No. 129 (1944 Nov 13) (Box 81, Folder 373)
    - Moore-McCormack Lines, Inc. v. McMahon, No. 316 (1956 May 7) (Box 81, Folder 374)
    - Moore v. Central Railroad Company of New Jersey, No. 41 (1950 Oct 30) (Box 81, Folder 375)
    - Moore v. Waring, No. 16 (1952 Nov 3) (Box 81, Folder 376)
    - Moran Transportation Corporation, Petition of, No. 52 (1950 Oct 30) (Box 81, Folder 377)
    - Morgan v. United States of America, No. 15 (1955 Oct 10), 1956 (Box 81, Folder 378)
    - Morris Plan Industrial Bank of New York v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 14 (1945 Oct 8) (Box 81, Folder 379)
    - Morris v. Pennsylvania Railroad Company, No. 159 (1951 Jan 8) (Box 81, Folder 380)
    - Morse v. Commissioner of Internal Revenue, No. 98 (1953 Jan 12) (Box 81, Folder 381)
    - Mottolese v. Honorable Samuel H. Kaufman (1949 May 2) (Box 81, Folder 382)
    - Murphy v. Overlakes Freight Corporation, No. 23 (1949 Oct 10) (Box 81, Folder 383)
    - Murray v. Schwartz, No. 246 (1949 May 2) (Box 81, Folder 384)
    - Nachman Spring-Filled Corporation v. Kay Manufacturing Corp., No. 59 (1943 Oct 11) (Box 81, Folder 385)
    - National Browne Co., Inc., In re, No. 75 (1945 Oct 8) (Box 81, Folder 386)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Air Associates, Incorporated, No. 292 (1941 Jun 9) (Box 81, Folder 387)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. American Tube Bending Co., Inc., No. 266 (1953 May 11) (Box 81, Folder 388)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. American White Cross Laboratories, Inc., No. 141 (1947 Feb 3) (Box 81, Folder 389)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Cities Service Oil Company (1942 Jun 15) (Box 81, Folder 390)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Dinion Coil Company, No. 52 (1952 Nov 3) (Box 82, Folder 391)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Electronics Equipment Co., No. 120 (1951 Dec 10), 1952 (Box 82, Folder 392)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Gaynor News Company, Inc., No. 231 (1952 May 12) (Box 82, Folder 393)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Greater New York Broadcasting Corporation, No. 86 (1945 Jan 8) (Box 82, Folder 394)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Henry Heide, Inc., No. 66 (1954 Oct 4), 1955 (Box 82, Folder 395)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, et al., No. 235 (1956 Mar 12) (Box 82, Folder 396)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. International Hod Carriers' Building & Common Laborers' Union of America (1955 Nov 14) (Box 82, Folder 397)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Medo Photo Supply Corporation, No. 233 (1943 Apr 5) (Box 82, Folder 398)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Moyer and Pratt, Inc., No. 84 (1953 Nov 9) (Box 82, Folder 399)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. National Maritime Union of America, No. 189 (1949 Jun 6) (Box 82, Folder 400)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. New Britain Machine Co., No. 152 (1954 Jan 11) (Box 82, Folder 401)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Newspaper and Mail Deliverers' Union of New York and Hearst Publications, Nos. 43-44 (1951 Nov 5) (Box 82, Folder 402)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Remington Rand, Inc. (1942 Jul 27) (Box 82, Folder 403)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Service Trade Chauffers, et al., No. 46 (1950 Dec 11), 1951 (Box 82, Folder 404)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. The Office Towel Supply Company, Inc., No. 99 (1952 Dec 8), 1953 (Box 82, Folder 405)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. The Todd Company, Inc., No. 24 (1947 Mar 7), 1949 (Box 82, Folder 406)
    - National Labor Relations Board v. Universal Camera Corporation (1951 Jun 11) (Box 82, Folder 407)
    - National Motorship Corporation v. Hoey, No. 100 (1942 Oct 19) (Box 82, Folder 408)
    - New England Coal and Coke Company v. Rutland Railroad Company, No. 302 (1944 Apr 10) (Box 82, Folder 409)
    - Newman v. Clayton F. Summy Company, No. 71 (1942 Oct 19) (Box 82, Folder 410)
    - New York, City of v. Hall, No. 227 (1944 Jan 10) (Box 82, Folder 411)
    - New York, City of v. McLain Lines, Inc., No. 184 (1944 Dec 11), 1945 (Box 82, Folder 412)